Error: Please enable JavaScript in your browser before using this site.

Error: Please [enable cookies](https://mychart.et1270.epichosted.com/MyChart/Help/Cookies) to log in to MyChart.

Loading...

MyChart Username 

Password 

New User?
---------

Pay Online?
-----------

﻿

Epic Online Privacy
-------------------

### Policy Overview

This online privacy notice is provided to make you aware of the online privacy practices for EvergreenHealth Medical Center, EvergreenHealth Monroe, and EvergreenHealth Medical Group (collectively "EvergreenHealth," "our," "we," or "us"). This online privacy notice covers our online privacy practices with respect to use and/or disclosure of information we may collect from you when you access or use our MyChart. Reading it will help you understand your privacy rights.

EvergreenHealth.com does not passively collect personal information about you. The information collected includes the domain name from which you access the Internet, the IP address of your computer, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked to our website.

This information is used to validate traffic to MyChart. Some pages may collect information that does not personally identify you. This is done through a special tracking code that identifies how users use MyChart. Sometimes third-party service providers help us collect and analyze the data. Unless specifically stated otherwise, no additional information will be collected about you.

### Important Note Regarding Notice of Privacy Practices

This online privacy notice does not describe how we use or disclose any medical information. Please see the EvergreenHealth Notice of Privacy Practices for information on our [privacy practices regarding medical information](https://www.evergreenhealth.com/patients-visitors/patient-privacy/).

### About Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk that allows a server to recall information about your session while you're connected.

While visiting MyChart, you may encounter a webpage that uses cookies. Cookies that come from MyChart are not designed to collect personal information about you, only about your browser session. The cookie makes it easier for you to use some of the features of these webpages.

### Links to Third-Party Websites

MyChart contains links to websites operated by third parties. EvergreenHealth has no control over the policies of third-party sites. Be sure to review the terms of those sites for their practices.

### Online Payments

**What personal information does EvergreenHealth collect for online payments?**

If you make an online payment or donation, we ask you to provide the basic information necessary to process such requests, including:

* Name
* Mailing and billing address
* Phone number
* Email address
* Credit card information (type of card, account number, expiration date, CCV)

**How does EvergreenHealth use personal information for online payments?**

EvergreenHealth uses the personal information you supply for the purpose stated at the time it is collected. Other than the following exceptions, EvergreenHealth never shares, trades, sells or otherwise discloses personal payment information to third parties:

* We supply the information to the service providers and payment gateways that enable EvergreenHealth to process credit card payments through the website. Under their agreements with us, these third-party partners may not retain, share, store or use personal information for any secondary purposes.
* Credit card information may be stored to process refunds and/or recurring payments, as requested at the time of disclosure.
* We may be required to disclose the information by law, for example through applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas.

### Children's Privacy

We will never ask for or knowingly collect Personal Information from children (13 years of age and under) through our websites. If you are a child, you are not permitted to use MyChart and should immediately exit. If we are made aware that information from a child has been collected without verification of parental or guardian consent, we will delete this information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child, please contact us at info@evergreenhealthcare.org.

### Revisions

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Online Privacy Policy at any time by posting those changes in revisions to this Online Privacy Policy. The Online Privacy Policy may also be revised in response to changes in federal or state law. Your use of MyChart following the revisions will mean you accept these changes. Unless otherwise indicated, any revisions to this Online Privacy Policy will apply immediately upon posting to the Website.

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about this Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@evergreenhealthcare.org.

### Online Privacy Policy Last Updated

Updated: October 1, 2022

[MyChart® licensed from Epic Systems Corporation © 1999 - 2024](https://mychart.et1270.epichosted.com/MyChart/Authentication/Login?mode=stdfile&option=epiccopyright)
